(Leonard:)Would you please get that?
(Raj:)Of course.
(Sheldon:)Why do you have to make things
so complicated?
(Page:)Dr. Cooper?
(Leonard:)Yes.
(Woman at Door:)I'm Special Agent Page, FBI.
You say you're Special
Agent Page, FBI.
(Page:)Here's my I.D.
(Sheldon:)And here is
(Sheldon:)my Justice League
membership card.
(Sheldon:)But that doesn't
prove I know Batman.
(Page:)I just want to ask you a few
questions about Howard Wolowitz.
(Sheldon:)Oh. All right.
(Sheldon:)I doubt anyone
would risk
(Sheldon:)the stiff penalties for
impersonating a federal officer
(Sheldon:)just to ask questions about
a minor league engineer
(Sheldon:)with an unresolved
Oedipal complex.
(Woman at Door:)Thank you.
(Sheldon:)For the record,
I truly support the FBI
(Sheldon:)in the mission
which is expressed
(Sheldon:)through their motto...?